eyefortravel.com 2019-06-11

# Privacy Policy | Travel Industry News & Conferences - EyeforTravel

  1. **OVERVIEW**

This policy applies to personal information collected via websites owned or controlled by Eyefortravel Ltd and their brands (for a list of these brands, please see <http://fc-bi.com/>.) (collectively referred to in this policy as “we”, "us" or "our").

The aim of this policy is to explain how we use any personal information we collect, or that you provide through our websites, landing pages, emails or webforms.

We comply with the relevant data protection legislation for your region. If you are in the European Economic Area, this includes the General Data Protection Regulations and the Privacy and Electronic Communications Regulations.

If our Privacy Policy changes in any way, we will place an updated version on this page. Regularly reviewing this page ensures that you are always aware of what personal information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances, if any, we will share it with other parties.

  2. **WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?**

You do not have to give us any personal information in order to use most of our websites.

However, if you wish to subscribe to a service, download content, book a pass to our events, or request further information, we may collect the following personal information from you:

  * name, business phone number and business email address; and
  * job title, company name, company address, demographic information (such as country) and areas of professional interests.

We will also keep a record of any financial transaction you make with us but we do not directly collect, process or store your debit or credit card information. Online payments made through this website are processed securely by a third party payment provider Cvent. Please refer to paragraph 4 to understand how cvent process your payment card data.

In addition, we may automatically collect information about the website that you came from or are going to. We also collect information about the pages of our website which you visit, IP addresses, the type of browser you use and the times you access this website. Our marketing system uses this information to provide you with a smooth, efficient, and personalised experience while using our services.

  3. **PROCESSING YOUR PERSONAL DATA**

We will use the personal information we collect in order to:

  * provide information; and updates about our products when you request it;
  * administer our website and provide customer services;
  * meet legal, regulatory and compliance requirements;
  * gather management information to form statistical and trend analysis;
  * investigate any complaints about this website;
  * personalise your experience of this website; and
  * contact you about our products and services which we think might be of interest to you (where we have the appropriate permissions to do so; please see Paragraph 5 for more information).

We may employ the services of third party service providers to help us in certain areas, such as website hosting and maintenance; and in the provision of software such as our CRM system and marketing system. In some cases the third party may receive your information. However, at all times, we will control and be responsible for the use of your information.

We may use aggregated information so we can administer and improve our website, analyse trends, gather broad demographic information and detect suspicious or fraudulent transactions.

If you provide a credit or debit card, we may also use third parties to check the validity of the sort code, account number and card number you submit in order to prevent fraud as well as to process any transaction you attempt via the website.

  4. **THIRD PARTY PRIVACY POLICIES:**

**Oracle Eloqua:**[ **https://www.oracle.com/legal/privacy/index.html**](https://www.oracle.com/legal/privacy/index.html)

We use Oracle Eloqua as our Email Marketing System. Where we have the relevant permission (please see Paragraphs 3 & 5 for more information), your data will be processed by this system. 

**Cvent:**[ **http://www.cvent.com/en/privacy-policy.shtml**](http://www.cvent.com/en/privacy-policy.shtml)

We use Cvent as our Event Rigistration System. Where we have the relevant permission (please see Paragraphs 3 & 5 for more information), your data will be processed by this system. 

**Salesforce:**[ **https://www.salesforce.com/uk/company/privacy/**](https://www.salesforce.com/uk/company/privacy/)

We use Salesforce as our Customer Relationship Management (CRM) system. Where we have the relevant permission (please see Paragraphs 3 & 5 for more information), your data will be processed by this system.

**Google:**[ **https://policies.google.com/privacy**](https://policies.google.com/privacy)

We use google services: to analyse data visiting our websites (google analytics); to place and track paid search adverts on search engines (google adwords); and to re-target relevant adverts (google adwords). Please see paragraphs 3, 5 & 6 for more information)

  5. **TRANSFERRAL OF DATA OUTSIDE THE EUROPEAN ECONOMIC AREA**

We may transfer some of your personal information to the United States of America as our marketing system and CRM providers outsource to both these jurisdictions. These countries may not have equivalent data protection legislation to the UK. However, when we transfer your personal information in this way, we will keep it securely and only use it as outlined in this Privacy & Cookies Policy. By submitting your personal information to this website, you consent to such transfers taking place.

Where you have given us the appropriate permissions either during the registration process for our events; or in the process of accessing our content through online webforms, we may from time to time contact you by email, telephone or post about our products and services (from all of our brands) that may be of interest to you.

We may offer you complimentary content and ask you for your consent to allow us to process your personal data in exchange. Under the GDPR, we rely on legitimate interests to make your consent mandatory in exchange for our content provision. If you would like more information, please get in touch at [privacy@fc-bi.com](mailto:privacy@fc-bi.com).

If at any point, you would like to opt-out of receiving such marketing communications from us, please click on the unsubscribe link at the bottom of any emails you receive, or email us, stating your preferences, at [privacy@fc-bi.com](mailto:privacy@fc-bi.com).

  7. **USE OF COOKIES & TRACKING TECHNOLOGY**

**Use of Cookies on our website**

Cookies are small text files that are placed on your computer by websites that you visit. They are widely used in order to make websites work, or work more efficiently, as well as to provide information to the owners of the site. 

All cookies have expiration dates in them that determine how long they stay in your browser. Cookies can be removed in two ways: automatically, when they expire; or when you manually delete them. For more information on cookies, see: [http://www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/)

We use the following categories of cookies on our website:

**Necessary Cookies**

These cookies are essential in order to enable you to move around the website and use its features. Without these cookies, services you have asked for such as remembering your login details or shopping basket items cannot be provided.

**Performance Cookies**

These cookies collect information on how people use our website. They may be anonymous e.g. Google Analytics; or identifiable e.g. our email marketing system. Performance cookies help us understand how customers arrive at, browse or use our site, and highlight areas where we can improve our marketing campaigns.

**Functionality Cookies**

These cookies remember choices you make such as the country you visit our website from, and contact details. These can then be used to provide you with an experience more appropriate to your selections and to make the visits more tailored and pleasant.

**Targeting Cookies**

These cookies collect information about your browsing habits in order to make advertising more relevant to you and your interests. They are also used to limit the number of times you see an advert as well as help measure the effectiveness of an advertising campaign. The cookies are usually placed by third party advertising networks. They remember the websites you visit and that information is shared with us.

**Social Media Cookies**

These cookies allow you to share what you’ve been doing on the website on social media such as Facebook and Twitter. These cookies are not within our control. Please refer to the respective privacy policies for how their cookies work.

If you want to delete any cookies that are already on your computer, please refer to the help and support area on your internet browser for instructions on how to locate the file or directory that stores cookies.

Please note that by deleting our cookies or disabling future cookies you may not be able to access certain areas or features of our site. To find out more about cookies please visit: [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/)  or see [www.youronlinechoices.eu](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/)  which contains further information about behavioural advertising and online privacy.

We have implemented comprehensive technical and organisational measures designed to secure your personal information from accidental loss and from unauthorised access, use, alteration or disclosure. In the unlikely event of a data breach – we will notify you within 72 hours.

  9. **ACCESS TO YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**

You may review, correct, update or change the personal information we hold at any time. If you wish to do this, please contact us at [privacy@fc-bi.com](mailto:privacy@fc-bi.com). We may require you to provide verification of your identity before providing a copy of the personal information we hold.

If you have any questions about this statement or your personal information, please contact us at [privacy@fc-bi.com](mailto:privacy@fc-bi.com).
